{
    "quizTitle": "사칙연산 암산 훈련",
    "quizId": "m8mo6iupwxw8e",
    "version": 1,
    "questions": [{
        "questionBody": "16 + 28",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 44,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 44"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "34 - 18",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 16,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 16"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "14 × 3",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 42,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 42"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "42 - 17",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 25,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 25"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "38 + 26",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 64,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 64"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "8 × 22",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 176,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 176"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "51 ÷ 3",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 17,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 17"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "417 - 132",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 285,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 285"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "198 + 225",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 423,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 423"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "437 ÷ 23",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 19,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 19"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "25 × 32",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 800,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 800"
        }
    }, {
        "questionBody": "3927 + 4395",
        "type": "NumberAnswer",
        "correctAnswer": 8322,
        "help": {
            "summary": "정답은 8322"
        }
    }]
}
